TreePeople records, 1970s-2010 LSC.2180
UCLA Library Special Collections
TreePeople records
1970s-2010
LSC.2180
UCLA Library Special Collections
59.0 linear feet (82 boxes, 17 record cartons, 8 flat boxes, and 4 roll boxes)
The Los Angeles-based environmental group TreePeople is known for promoting environmental awareness and conducting educational outreach programs locally as well as internationally. The collection includes slides, photographs, audiovisual materials, clippings, correspondence, organization files, ephemera, and awards documenting the development and efforts of TreePeople.
TreePeople (Firm).
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF. Advance notice is required for access to the collection. Please contact UCLA Library Special Collections for paging information.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Andy Lipkis, President of TreePeople, 2013.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 7392484
History
TreePeople, a non-profit environmental organization, was founded by Andy Lipkis in Los Angeles in 1973. Originally called the California Conservation Project (CCP), the group was more commonly referred to as the "TreePeople," and was thus, renamed in 1974. Lipkis established the organization at the age of eighteen following his experiences at a leadership training program in the San Bernardino National forest. After attending the program, Lipkis directed his efforts toward establishing the CCP in order to provide people with environmental education and the opportunity to plant trees.
In 1977 TreePeople established their headquarters in Los Angeles on the grounds of a former fire station. The site was renamed Coldwater Canyon Park, and would later serve as TreePeople's Center for Community Forestry. Since its founding, TreePeople have worked to promote environmental awareness through city-wide tree planting programs, as well as environmental education and training for the local community, and on a global scale. TreePeople's efforts have included disaster-relief work, in addition to initiating significant urban planting projects. These projects include the Million Tree Campaign in 1981, which encouraged the planting of one million trees before the 1984 Los Angeles Summer Olympics; the Martin Luther King Boulevard Memorial Project, where three hundred trees were planted in a single day; and the Big Tree Campaign, an urban-planting project aimed at providing shade to homes, buildings, and large sun-exposed spaces in and around the greater Los Angeles area.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material related to the Los Angeles based environmental organization, TreePeople. The collection includes slides, photographs, audiovisual materials, clippings, correspondence, organization files, ephemera, and awards documenting the development and efforts of TreePeople. The materials represent assorted TreePeople events and programs such as their Urban Forestry program, Million Tree Campaign, King Boulevard Memorial Project, public school outreach, and disaster relief work, among other undertakings.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Organization Files
Press Clippings
Photographic Materials
Awards
Audiovisual Materials
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
COLLECTION CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Related Material
Interview of Andy Lipkis [oral history transcript] / Jane Collings, interviewer. UCLA Library Center for Oral History Research, 2006-2007.
TreePeople (Firm). -- Archives; Environmentalists-California--Los Angeles--Archives.; Tree planting--California--Los Angeles--Citizen participation; Urban forestry--California--Los Angeles--Citizen participation
- Organization Files, 1970-2010 and undated
  Scope and Content
  The series consists of correspondence, notes, articles, and ephemera related to TreePeople’s local, national, and international community activities and events. Projects represented include King Boulevard Memorial Project, Million Tree Campaign, Urban Forestry, international tree planting efforts, and school programs, among others. Additionally, there is a small amount of board meeting minutes and annual reports; reports and proposals created by TreePeople and other organizations; promotional brochures, mailers, and cards, and a small amount of ephemera. There is no specific arrangement to the series; the series may contain duplicative material.
  - Board Meeting, 1993 Jun 13 (Box 90)
  - Board Meeting, 1994 Jan 26 (Box 90)
  - Board Minutes, 1993 Sep 12 (Box 90)
  - Board Minutes, 1993 Apr 18 (Box 90)
  - Board Minutes, 1994 Jun 5 (Box 90)
  - Board Minutes, 1994 Mar 20 (Box 90)
  - Board Minutes, 1993 Dec 5 (Box 90)
  - Board Stuff, 1986 (Box 85)
  - 1984 Olympics, 1980-1981 (Box 87)
  - 20 years in Coldwater Canyon slideshow script, 1997 (Box 97)
  - Africa Fruit Tree, 1983-1990 (Box 82)
  - Africa Fruit Tree Project - project evaluation, ca. 1980s (Box 85)
  - Africa maps, no date (Box 86)
  - African Fruit Tree Partnership Program (The), 1989 (Box 82)
  - Air Quality LA City Planning, 1980-1981 (Box 85)
  - An Urban Forestry Program for California, 1977 (Box 81)
  - Andy Lipkis Assorted lists and correspondence, 1978 (Box 85)
  - Andy Lipkis Chipko article for Co-Evolution Quarterly, 1981 Aug (Box 85)
  - Andy Lipkis film rights people, ca. 1980s (Box 86)
  - Andy Lipkis personal records, ca. 1970s (Box 86)
  - Andy Lipkis speaking engagements, ca. 1980s (Box 88)
  - Andy Lipkis speeches, ca. 1980s (Box 88)
  - Animation cell for Once Upon a Forest, undated (Box 108)
    General note
    Signed by Bill Hanna.
  - Artist rendering TreePeople Center for Community Forestry, ca. 2000s (Box 108)
  - Australia, 1985-1992 (Box 82)
  - Auto shade mock-up and correspondence, 1987 (Box 75)
  - Backyard Planting Workbook, 1990 Aug 11 (Box 86)
  - Bayview Hunters Point Urban Forestry Initiative, 1979 (Box 80)
  - Big Tree Campaign - Working Paper Discussion of a Major Urban Forestry Program - Revision B, 1989 (Box 83)
  - Big Tree Campaign Budget Outlines, 1989-1991 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign Chronicle, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign Committee Meeting Notes and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign correspondence and program notes, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign Summaries, undated (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: Committee Organization, Agendas, Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: community organizing, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: Executive Summary, ca. 1990s (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: Executive Summary, Strategic Outline, Synopsis, etc., undated (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: Index, 1990 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: Marc Brody, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: original city plan, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: retreat, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: two page overview, undated (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: Urban Tree Planting to Combat Global Warming by Andy and Katie Lipkis, 1990 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: Working Paper Discussion of a Major Urban Forestry Program - Revision A, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Big Tree Campaign: Working Paper Discussion of a Major Urban Forestry Program - Revision B, Review Draft, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Brown's Canyon, 1979 (Box 80)
  - Bumper sticker mock-up and correspondence, 1987 (Box 75)
  - California Conservation Project and TreePeople patches, undated (Box 99)
  - California Conservation Project Id Card Forms, undated (Box 86)
  - California Conservation Project round seal embosser, undated (Box 99)
  - Campaign Green Streets, 1994 (Box 96)
  - Campus Forestry workshop packet, 1993, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Children of the Green Earth, 1978-1982 (Box 80)
  - Chipko, undated (Box 82)
  - Citizen Forester manual, 2009 (Box 95)
  - Community Relations & Outreach Program (CROP), 1992-1993 (Box 95)
  - Constitution Bicentennial, 1986 (Box 85)
  - Cool Schools teacher packets (pre and post activities), undated (Box 94)
  - Cooling Our Communities: Guidebook on Tree Planting and Light-Colored Surfacing (A) - by Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1992 (Box 89)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Correspondence - Bruce and Ele Farrow, 1984-2001 (Box 112)
  - Correspondence and notes concerning various TreePeople projects (2 folders), ca. 1980s (Box 86)
  - Correspondence concerning Million Tree Campaign, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
  - Council Wilkinson's Valley Tree Plantings, 1974 (Box 81)
  - Crann, 1987-1991 (Box 83)
  - Crenshaw High School Site Project: team 3 design charrette, undated (Box 93)
    With small amount of negatives.
  - Crenshaw Neighbors and King Boulevard Project, ca. 1980s-2000s (Box 112)
  - Culver City Urban Forest Project correspondence and loose papers, 1973-1981 (Box 79)
    With unrelated clippings concerning TreePeople or general environmental issues.
  - Culver City Urban Forest: Final Report Submitted to California Department of Forestry: project of TreePeople (A), 1981 (Box 90)
  - Drawings and plans for zoning and drainage, undated (Box 107)
    Appears related to Los Angeles Community Design Center.
  - Early Andy Lipkis articles, 1970s (Box 85)
  - England, 1984-1991 (Box 82)
  - Environmental Education Information, 1980 (Box 79)
  - Facsimiles of letters and notes mounted on foam board (appears to be exhibit items), 1973 (Box 105)
  - Facsimiles of letters mounted on foam board (appears to be exhibit items), 1973 (Box 101)
  - Final Report: Los Angeles Urban Forest: project of TreePeople for the California Department of Forestry (A) (two copies), 1983 (Box 90)
  - Findhorn Foundation, 1984-1992 (Box 82)
  - Forest of London, 1987-1992 (Box 83)
  - Forestry ephemera, 1990-1992 (Box 95)
  - Forests in a Changing Climate - edited by Dr. Ata Qureshi; Climate Institute, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 89)
    North American Conference on Forestry Responses to Climate Change, May 1990.
  - Fruit Tree Workshop Training Manual, 1989 (Box 82)
  - General Telephone, ca. 1980s (Box 88)
  - George Parks, Development, 1986 (Box 85)
  - Global Seeds, 1985-1987 (Box 83)
  - Global Study Group, 1985 (Box 83)
  - Global Study Nights, 1985 (Box 83)
  - Going Global: correspondence and notes, 1989-1990 (Box 84)
  - Grant billings, 1979-1981 (Box 82)
  - Green Brochure (in Spanish), undated (Box 81)
  - Green Guardian ephemera, 1992 (Box 95)
  - Greening Australia, 1983-1988 (Box 83)
  - Guidelines for Developing and Evaluating Tree Ordinances: Prepared by Elizabeth A. Bernhardt and Tedmund J. Swiecki (Plant Science Consulting and Research) for California Department of Forestry and Fire Protection, Urban Forestry Program, 1991 (Box 90)
  - Harvest Moon programs, 1990-1992 (Box 95)
  - Helen Minor (file), ca. 1970s - ca. 1980s (Box 97)
    Correspondence, clippings, ephemera, and photographs that appears related to Helen Minor, Andy Lipkis, the California Conservation Project and TreePeople.
  - Helen Minor (oversize), 1981 and undated (Box 41)
  - How to Plant (in Spanish), undated (Box 81)
  - Ideas File, ca. 1970s- ca. 1980s (Box 85)
  - Industrial Site Project: team 1 design charrette, 1997 (Box 99)
  - Industrial Site Project: team 1 design charrette illustrated notes, 1997 (Box 101)
  - Inspiration, undated (Box 81)
  - International-Czechoslovakia, Ekologica Spolecnost, undated (Box 82)
  - Inter-Religious Project, Million Tree Campaign, ca. 1980s (Box 88)
  - Ireland, 1985 (Box 83)
  - Itinerary, Africa, 1987 Aug (Box 86)
  - Jeri Eckhart, 1989-1991 (Box 83)
  - Jewish Journal correspondence, 1996 (Box 96)
    With photographs.
  - KCBS Video Footage Log, 1980,1991,1994 (Box 69)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project, ca. 1990 (Box 92)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project assorted correspondence, papers, and ephemera, ca. 1989 - ca. 1990 (Box 91)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project assorted correspondence, papers, and ephemera, 1990 Jan 13 (Box 91)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project assorted notes, clippings, and ephemera (2 folders), ca. 1990 (Box 93)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project assorted reports and notes concerning finances, 1990-1991 (Box 91)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project caregivers' list and block captain master list, ca. 1990 (Box 92)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project caregivers' list and tree care commitment sheets, ca. 1990 (Box 91)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project donation thank you letters, 1990 (Box 98)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project ephemera, 1990 (Box 91)
    With VHS tape.
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project evaluation forms, ca. 1990 (Box 91)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project future planting, undated (Box 91)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project income correspondence and notes, 1990 (Box 98)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project letterhead and brochures, 1990 (Box 92)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project Planting Supervisor Training, 1990 Jan 6 (Box 91)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project posters, 1990 (Box 101)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project receipts, 1990 (Box 98)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project sign-in sheets, ca. 1990 (Box 92)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project street tree planting, ca. 1990-1991 (Box 92)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project Tree Care, ca. 1990 (Box 91)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project Tree Care Task Force, ca. 1990 (Box 92)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project t-shirts (2 items), undated (Box 102)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project volunteer and donation information, ca. 1990 (Box 92)
  - King Boulevard Memorial Project volunteer information, ca. 1990 (Box 91)
  - LA County Sanitation Department Agreement, 1978 (Box 80)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Review Feasibility Study, Draft Interim Report and Environmental Impact Statement - publication by U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Los Angeles District Planning Division, 1991 (Box 89)
  - Los Angeles Urban Forest (The): A project of Tree People (2 folders with three copies), ca. 1980s (Box 88)
  - Marina Freeway Urban Forest Run assorted correspondence, notes, and ephemera, 1979-1982 (Box 93)
  - Masters of the New City - submitted by TreePeople with ReThink, Inc., PS Enterprises and Center for Environmental Education Program (environmental education proposal), 1996 (Box 96)
  - Million Tree Campaign - Thanks, ca. 1980s (Box 88)
  - Million Tree Campaign education program, 1981-1984 (Box 87)
  - Million Tree Campaign loose papers and ephemera, ca. 1980s (Box 88)
  - Million tree countdown tally sheets and plantation documentation, 1981-1984 (Box 69)
  - Million Tree Plan (2 folders), 1981-1983 (Box 87)
  - Million Trees documentation, ca. 1980s (Box 88)
  - Mounted photographs used in exhibits, undated (Box 105)
  - Multi-family Site Project: team 2 design charrette, 1997 (Box 98)
  - Multiple Approach to Urban Forestry (A): The Oakland Experience by Isabel M. Wade, undated (Box 81)
  - National Tree Trust Act of 1990 and America the Beautiful Initiative, 1990-1991 (Box 96)
    With signed letter from George Bush.
  - National Urban Forestry Conference, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1982 Oct (Box 81)
  - New Forests Fund, 1983-1985 (Box 83)
  - Olympic Forest, 1984-1985 (Box 87)
  - Olympic Forest, 1984-1985 (Box 88)
  - On Balance: Weighing the Costs and Benefits of Urban Trees by Cheryl Kollin, ASLA (a cooperative project by: US Forest Service Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, University of California, Berkeley; City of San Jose, and San Jose Beautiful), 1991 Apr 20 (Box 90)
  - Organizational development, ca. 1980s (Box 86)
  - Patterns of Lumber Salvage in the Los Angeles Basin by Kelly Wade in cooperation with the USDA Forest Service, Pacific Southwest Forest and Range Experiment Station - final report, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Planters' Guide to the Urban Forest (A) - report by TreePeople, 1983 (Box 79)
  - Planting/Training, 1977 Aug (Box 81)
  - Poland-Bialowieza National Park, 1989 (Box 83)
  - Potting Program, 1975-1976 (Box 80)
  - Press Releases, 1981 (Box 79)
  - Press Releases, 1975-1977 (Box 79)
  - Press Releases, 1979 (Box 79)
  - Press Releases, 1978 (Box 79)
  - Project drawings and site plans, undated (Box 106)
    Trees charrette single-family residence plans and items that appear related to Crenshaw High School Site Project: team 3 design charrette.
  - Project drawings and site plans, undated (Box 110)
    Items appear related to Industrial Site Project: team 1 design charrette.
  - Project drawings and site plans, undated (Box 111)
    Appears related to commercial site plan near Pico and Cloverfield.
  - Project Tree House: A Continuing Environmental Education and Participation Program: proposal of the California Conservation Project TreePeople (A) (2 copies), 1978-1979 (Box 90)
  - Public Service Announcements (PSAs), 1982-1983 (Box 79)
  - Rainforest Information Centre, 1990 (Box 83)
  - Relaxation of Queensland Limited, 1991 (Box 83)
  - Right Livelihood Foundation (The) correspondence and ephemera, ca. 1980s (Box 86)
  - School Programs ephemera, 1990-1992 (Box 94)
  - School Programs thank you letters to TreePeople, 1990-1991 (Box 94)
  - School Programs: Sun Valley Watershed Project, 2003 (Box 94)
  - School Programs: The Magical City Forest: A Teacher's Guide to the Urban Forest, 1994 (Box 94)
  - School Programs: The Magical City Forest: A Teacher's Guide to the Urban Forest, 1994 (Box 94)
    Same content, different cover
  - School Programs: The Magical City Forest: A Teacher's Guide to the Urban Forest, 2010 (Box 94)
  - School Programs: TreePeople's Campus Forestry Program: Student Involvement, Schoolyard Explorers, ca. 2000s (Box 94)
  - Script - The Andy Lipkis Story, 1985 Jan 22 (Box 86)
  - Second Californian Urban Forestry Symposium, Cal Poly Pomona, 1982 Jan (Box 82)
  - Second Quarter Implementation, 1992-1993 (Box 82)
  - Seed Promotion Material, undated (Box 84)
  - Seedling Art, undated (Box 95)
  - Shade Tree Conservation Program: An S.C.E. and Customer Partnership Program (General Plan), Prepared for Southern California Edison Environmental Research Department, Prepared by Urban Forestry Consultants, 1991 Aug (Box 90)
  - Simple Act of Planting a Tree (The) - statistics of trees (illustrations), undated (Box 95)
  - Simple Act of Planting a Tree (The) press kit, 1990 (Box 93)
  - Simple Act of Planting a Tree: A Citizen Forestry Guide (The) by TreePeople, undated (Box 77)
  - Smog Tolerant Tree Planting Program art boards, ca. 1980 (Box 93)
  - Staff and staff roles, ca. 1980s (Box 86)
  - State of World Rural Poverty (The): Profile of Latin America and the Caribbean (A) - publication by IFAD (International Fund for Agricultural Development), 1993 (Box 89)
  - Summer Program for Disadvantage Youth (SPEDY) and correspondence regarding Harbor Gateway Beautification, 1978-1984 (Box 80)
  - Sun Valley past media, ca. 2000-2003 (Box 112)
    Informational literature and clippings related to the Sun Valley Park Multiuse Project
  - T.R.E.E.S. promotional umbrella, undated (Box 101)
  - Taking it to the Streets plan, undated (Box 96)
  - Target: 200 Million Trees, 1987-1989 (Box 83)
  - Teachers guide take home piece, ca. 1998-2000 (Box 94)
  - The Forest of Kaboo, undated (Box 94)
  - Timber Management Plan, 1976 (Box 80)
  - Transagency Resources for Environmental and Economic Sustainability (T.R.E.E.S): proposal for Urban Watershed Management (A) - by TreePeople, 1994-1995 (Box 90)
  - Tree Boy Review, 1978 (Box 79)
  - Tree Group Report for US Forest Service, 1987-1991 (Box 83)
  - Tree Guide Illustrations, undated (Box 100)
  - Tree Guide Illustrations, undated (Box 101)
  - Tree People speech, 1984 (Box 87)
  - Tree Planting Campaign press release and associated documents, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Tree Project (Melbourne), 1989 (Box 83)
  - TreePeople Agreements, 1978-1979 (Box 85)
  - TreePeople Annual Reports, ca. 1989 - ca. 1999 (Box 95)
  - TreePeople art boards, undated (Box 100)
  - TreePeople art boards and transparencies, undated (Box 93)
  - TreePeople assorted papers, clippings, correspondence, and ephemera, 1979 - ca. 1990s (Box 97)
    Items appear to be unrelated
  - TreePeople Beginnings press-like packet, 1970-1982 (Box 97)
  - TreePeople brochure proofs, undated (Box 96)
  - TreePeople brochures, mailers and promotional material, ca. 1970s - ca. 2000s (Box 99)
  - TreePeople bumper stickers and decal stickers, ca. 1980s (Box 99)
  - TreePeople Center, ca. 2000s (Box 112)
  - TreePeople Docent and Volunteer program, ca. 1979 - 1990s (Box 95)
    Docent program manual, Volunteer Award Presentation (1991), volunteer brochure and certificate of appreciation.
  - TreePeople Forestry Team goals, 1983 (Box 96)
  - TreePeople greeting cards, 1992 (Box 95)
  - TreePeople Headquarters guide, undated (Box 100)
  - TreePeople license plate frame, ca. 1984 (Box 99)
  - TreePeople literature and flyers for events, 1978-1980 (Box 93)
  - TreePeople Logo Sheet, 1996 (Box 100)
  - TreePeople logos, undated (Box 86)
  - TreePeople Nameless Newsletter (1 folder), 1979 Jul-Aug 1979 (Box 74)
  - TreePeople News Newsletter, 1974, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 78)
  - TreePeople News Weekly, 1970s (Box 112)
  - TreePeople Press Kit, ca. 2005 (Box 112)
  - TreePeople programs and promotional literature, ca. 1996-2000s (Box 112)
    Brochures and flyers related to TreePeople Fruit Tree Program, Green Series, and Forestry Program.
  - TreePeople programs and promotional literature, undated (Box 112)
  - TreePeople promotional mailers, invitations, and brochures, ca. 1980s - ca. 2000s (Box 98)
  - TreePeople Proposal, 1983 Jan 16 (Box 89)
  - TreePeople Seedling News newsletters (1 folder), 1979 Aug-Mar 1981 (Box 74)
  - TreePeople Seedling News newsletters (14 folders), 1981-1983, 1986-1989 (Box 78)
  - TreePeople Seminar transcript, 1997 May 14 (Box 97)
  - TreePeople stickers, undated (Box 112)
  - TreePeople Timeline - promotional material, undated (Box 97)
  - TreePeople Volunteer Calendar of Events, 1992-1997 (Box 96)
  - TreePeople: Beyond LA Business Plan Formation, 1990 (Box 84)
  - Trees for 1932 Olympics, ca. 1930s, ca. 1980s (Box 87)
    With articles documenting tree planting for 1932 Olympics and 1980s tree planting plan documents.
  - Urban Conservation, 1987 (Box 82)
  - Urban Forest, 1977-1978 (Box 80)
  - Urban Forest, 1974-1977 (Box 80)
  - Urban Forest, 1974-1982 (Box 80)
  - Urban Forest (The): Journey into the Future by Awakening the Myth (A) - paper by Jade Satterthwaite, Department of Landscape Architecture, School of Environmental Design, California State Polytechnic University, Pomona (two copies), 1983 Mar 23 (Box 89)
  - Urban Forest art boards and posters (3 folders), ca. 1980s (Box 108)
  - Urban Forest conference, 1991 Nov 12-17 (Box 96)
  - Urban Forest television spot storyboard, ca. 1980s (Box 108)
    Appears to feature Gregory Peck.
  - Urban forestry, 1970s - ca. 1980 (Box 81)
    Ephemera concerning urban forestry programs unrelated to TreePeople.
  - Urban Forestry Conference, 1973 Mar 12-15 (Box 81)
  - Urban Forestry Conference, Washington, 1978 Nov 13-16 (Box 82)
  - Urban Forestry documentation, 1977-1979 (Box 81)
    Correspondence and ephemera
  - Urban Forestry meetings, 1978 Jan (Box 81)
  - Urban Forestry papers, undated (Box 81)
  - Urban Forestry publicity, 1978 (Box 81)
  - Urban Forestry slide show, undated (Box 81)
  - Urban Forestry Speech: Santa Cruz Urban Interface Symposium, 1981 Nov (Box 81)
  - Urban Forestry Symposium, 1978 May 19-20 (Box 81)
  - Urban Forestry training, 1986 (Box 85)
  - Urban Forestry TV spots, 1979 (Box 81)
  - Urban Forests newsletters and brochures, 1990 (Box 83)
    Publications by Forestry Commission, not TreePeople publications
  - Water Cycle Learning Objectives, 1993 (Box 94)